{
    "question": "hi",
    "answer": "Hey Clarkie"
}
{
    "question": "Give me the links related to Grad Admissions",
    "answer": "Apply: [Graduate Admissions Application](<a href=\"https://gradapply.clarku.edu/apply/?_gl=1*13hqkhx*_gcl_au*NTE4MzI0MTAuMTcwODQ4MzE1Mg..*_ga*MTExMzYxNDAzMi4xNzA4NDgzMTUy*_ga_8T1G50QTBE*MTcxMDE5NzEzMC4yLjEuMTcxMDE5NzE0NC40Ni4wLjM1MDc5NTI0NA..)\">https://gradapply.clarku.edu/apply/?_gl=1*13hqkhx*_gcl_au*NTE4MzI0MTAuMTcwODQ4MzE1Mg..*_ga*MTExMzYxNDAzMi4xNzA4NDgzMTUy*_ga_8T1G50QTBE*MTcxMDE5NzEzMC4yLjEuMTcxMDE5NzE0NC40Ni4wLjM1MDc5NTI0NA..)</a>"
}
{
    "question": "thanks",
    "answer": "Take care!, thanks for visiting Clark University Chatbot"
}
{
    "question": "hi",
    "answer": "Hi Clarkie, Good day!"
}
{
    "question": "Give me the links related to Grad Admissions",
    "answer": "Apply: [Graduate Admissions Application](<a href=\"https://gradapply.clarku.edu/apply/?_gl=1*13hqkhx*_gcl_au*NTE4MzI0MTAuMTcwODQ4MzE1Mg..*_ga*MTExMzYxNDAzMi4xNzA4NDgzMTUy*_ga_8T1G50QTBE*MTcxMDE5NzEzMC4yLjEuMTcxMDE5NzE0NC40Ni4wLjM1MDc5NTI0NA..)\">https://gradapply.clarku.edu/apply/?_gl=1*13hqkhx*_gcl_au*NTE4MzI0MTAuMTcwODQ4MzE1Mg..*_ga*MTExMzYxNDAzMi4xNzA4NDgzMTUy*_ga_8T1G50QTBE*MTcxMDE5NzEzMC4yLjEuMTcxMDE5NzE0NC40Ni4wLjM1MDc5NTI0NA..)</a>"
}
{
    "question": "hi",
    "answer": "Hey Clarkie"
}
{
    "question": "Give me the links related to Grad Admissions",
    "answer": "Inquire: [Graduate Admissions Inquiry](<a href=\"https://www.clarku.edu/graduate-education/request-info/?ga)\">https://www.clarku.edu/graduate-education/request-info/?ga)</a>"
}
{
    "question": "hi",
    "answer": "Hi Clarkie, what can I do for you?"
}
{
    "question": "Give me the links related to Grad Admissions",
    "answer": "Apply: [Graduate Admissions Application](<a href=\"https://gradapply.clarku.edu/apply/?_gl=1*13hqkhx*_gcl_au*NTE4MzI0MTAuMTcwODQ4MzE1Mg..*_ga*MTExMzYxNDAzMi4xNzA4NDgzMTUy*_ga_8T1G50QTBE*MTcxMDE5NzEzMC4yLjEuMTcxMDE5NzE0NC40Ni4wLjM1MDc5NTI0NA..)\">https://gradapply.clarku.edu/apply/?_gl=1*13hqkhx*_gcl_au*NTE4MzI0MTAuMTcwODQ4MzE1Mg..*_ga*MTExMzYxNDAzMi4xNzA4NDgzMTUy*_ga_8T1G50QTBE*MTcxMDE5NzEzMC4yLjEuMTcxMDE5NzE0NC40Ni4wLjM1MDc5NTI0NA..)</a>"
}
{
    "question": "hi",
    "answer": "Hey Clarkie"
}
{
    "question": "Give me the links related to Grad Admissions",
    "answer": "Inquire: [Graduate Admissions Inquiry](<a href=\"https://www.clarku.edu/graduate-education/request-info/?ga)\">https://www.clarku.edu/graduate-education/request-info/?ga)</a>"
}
{
    "question": "hi ",
    "answer": "Hi Clarkie, Good day!"
}
{
    "question": "Can you provide information about the faculty members in the Computer Science department at Clark University",
    "answer": "For professor-related details, please visit \ud83e\udd29 <a href=\"https://apps.clarku.edu/course-listings/registrar-SPS-grad-spring,24?_gl=1*y419a*_gcl_au*MTQ2NDk0ODU3LjE3MTI0MjUzNzg.\">https://apps.clarku.edu/course-listings/registrar-SPS-grad-spring,24?_gl=1*y419a*_gcl_au*MTQ2NDk0ODU3LjE3MTI0MjUzNzg.</a>"
}
{
    "question": "hey",
    "answer": "Hi Clarkie, what can I do for you?"
}
{
    "question": "hello",
    "answer": "Hello Clarkie, Feel free to ask me anything about Clark University."
}
{
    "question": "hey",
    "answer": "Hey Clarkie"
}
{
    "question": "siri",
    "answer": "Hey Clarkie"
}
{
    "question": "hey",
    "answer": "Hello Clarkie, Feel free to ask me anything about Clark University."
}
{
    "question": "hello",
    "answer": "Hi Clarkie, Good day!"
}
{
    "question": "hey",
    "answer": "Hello Clarkie, Feel free to ask me anything about Clark University."
}
{
    "question": "hello",
    "answer": "Hey Clarkie"
}
{
    "question": "Hi ",
    "answer": "Hi, what can I do for you?"
}
{
    "question": "Hi ",
    "answer": "Hello Clarkie, Feel free to ask me anything about Clark University."
}
{
    "question": "Hi ",
    "answer": "Hello Clarkie, Feel free to ask me anything about Clark University."
}
{
    "question": "testsai@clarku.edu",
    "answer": "Hi Clarkie, how can I help?"
}
{
    "question": "what majors does Clark University offer",
    "answer": "At Clark University, you can choose from a variety of majors such as Computer Science, Sociology, History, and many others."
}
{
    "question": "What is the tuition cost at Clark University",
    "answer": "Tuition fees at Clark University can vary based on the program and student status. It's best to check their website for the most up-to-date information."
}
{
    "question": "What are the housing options for students at Clark University",
    "answer": "Clark University offers various housing options for students, including residence halls and apartment-style living. You can choose from single, double, or suite-style accommodations."
}
{
    "question": "housing options",
    "answer": "Housing at Clark University is assigned on a first-come, first-served basis. Students can apply for housing through the university's housing portal and select their preferences for roommates and housing options."
}
{
    "question": "What are the admission requirements for international students at Clark University",
    "answer": "International students interested in Clark University must meet certain admission requirements, including submitting transcripts, English proficiency test scores, and a statement of purpose."
}
{
    "question": "admission requirements",
    "answer": "Inquire: [Graduate Admissions Inquiry](<a href=\"https://www.clarku.edu/graduate-education/request-info/?ga)\">https://www.clarku.edu/graduate-education/request-info/?ga)</a>"
}
{
    "question": "What scholarships are available at Clark University",
    "answer": "Scholarships available at Clark University include merit-based scholarships, need-based scholarships, and scholarships for underrepresented students. You can find more information on their website."
}
{
    "question": "scholorships available ",
    "answer": "Hi Clarkie, how can I help?"
}
{
    "question": "opt",
    "answer": "Please visit clark website for more details <a> https://www.clarku.edu</a>"
}
{
    "question": "cpt",
    "answer": "Students must complete two full-time semesters (does not include summer) in the United States before they qualify for CPT. Exceptions to the one academic year requirement are provided for students enrolled in graduate studies that require immediate participation in curricular practical training. "
}
{
    "question": "Does Clark University offer STEM OPT for international students",
    "answer": "Yes, STEM OPT (Optional Practical Training) is available for international students."
}
{
    "question": "stem opt",
    "answer": "Elective Subjects are Research and Marketing Analytics, IoT: Securing Communication Technologies through Data Analysis, Applied Deep Learning, Health Data and Record Systems, Special Topics: Data Analytics, Health Informatics, Independent Study (To be approved by advisor for topics like Sentiment Analysis, AI, Text Recognition, etc.), Capstone Practicum"
}
{
    "question": "oncampus jobs",
    "answer": "All the on campus jobs are posted on Handshake. Please check the posted part time on campus jobs on Handshake. "
}
{
    "question": "hi ",
    "answer": "Hi Clarkie, Good day!"
}
{
    "question": "housing offcampus",
    "answer": "Please visit clark website for more details <a> https://www.clarku.edu</a>"
}
{
    "question": "What options are available for graduate student housing, both on and off-campus",
    "answer": "You can visit our housing page to see housing options: <a href=\"https://www.clarku.edu/offices/housing/on-campus-housing/graduate-housing/\">https://www.clarku.edu/offices/housing/on-campus-housing/graduate-housing/</a>"
}
{
    "question": "helo",
    "answer": "Hey Clarkie"
}
{
    "question": "hjgfhgfh",
    "answer": "Hi Clarkie, Good day!"
}
{
    "question": "housing",
    "answer": "Please visit clark website for more details <a> https://www.clarku.edu</a>"
}
{
    "question": "hey",
    "answer": "Hi Clarkie, what can I do for you?"
}
{
    "question": "how are you",
    "answer": "Please visit clark website for more details <a> https://www.clarku.edu</a>"
}
{
    "question": "hello",
    "answer": "Hi Clarkie, what can I do for you?"
}
{
    "question": "hey",
    "answer": "Hello Clarkie, Feel free to ask me anything about Clark University."
}
{
    "question": "Hey",
    "answer": "Hello Clarkie, Feel free to ask me anything about Clark University."
}
{
    "question": "what majors does clark university offers",
    "answer": "Clark University offers a wide range of majors including Biology, Psychology, Economics, and more. You can find the full list on their website."
}
{
    "question": "what majors does clark university offers",
    "answer": "Clark University offers a wide range of majors including Biology, Psychology, Economics, and more. You can find the full list on their website."
}
{
    "question": "what majors does clark university offers",
    "answer": "Majors at Clark University vary and cover areas like Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics, and many more."
}
{
    "question": "hey",
    "answer": "Hey Clarkie"
}
{
    "question": "what majors does clark university offer",
    "answer": "Majors at Clark University vary and cover areas like Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics, and many more."
}
{
    "question": "what is the tuition cost at clark university",
    "answer": "To get an accurate estimate of tuition costs at Clark University, you should visit their website or contact the admissions office."
}
{
    "question": "what are admission requirements for international students",
    "answer": "Admission requirements for international students at Clark University include submitting academic transcripts, English language proficiency scores, and a statement of purpose. It's also important to meet the application deadlines."
}
{
    "question": "what are the housing options for students at clark university",
    "answer": "Housing facilities at Clark University include residence halls with amenities such as common lounges, study areas, and laundry facilities. Some halls also offer special interest housing options."
}
{
    "question": "what are the housing options for students",
    "answer": "You can apply for Optional Practical Training (OPT) up to 90 days before completing your degree program and up to 60 days after completing your degree program. It's recommended to apply as early as possible within this timeframe to allow for processing delay "
}
{
    "question": "what are the housing options for students at clark university ",
    "answer": "Housing facilities at Clark University include residence halls with amenities such as common lounges, study areas, and laundry facilities. Some halls also offer special interest housing options."
}
{
    "question": "admission requirements",
    "answer": "Bye! Come back again soon, thanks for visiting Clark University Chatbot."
}
{
    "question": "what are the admission requirements for international students at clark university",
    "answer": "Admission requirements for international students at Clark University include submitting academic transcripts, English language proficiency scores, and a statement of purpose. It's also important to meet the application deadlines."
}
{
    "question": "what scholarships are available at clark university",
    "answer": "Clark University offers several scholarships for eligible students, including merit-based scholarships, need-based scholarships, and scholarships for specific majors or programs."
}
{
    "question": "oncampus jobs",
    "answer": "All the on campus jobs are posted on Handshake. Please check the posted part time on campus jobs on Handshake. "
}
{
    "question": "cpt",
    "answer": "Students must complete two full-time semesters (does not include summer) in the United States before they qualify for CPT. Exceptions to the one academic year requirement are provided for students enrolled in graduate studies that require immediate participation in curricular practical training. "
}
{
    "question": "stemopt",
    "answer": "Bye! Come back again soon, thanks for visiting Clark University Chatbot."
}
{
    "question": "stem opt",
    "answer": "Please visit clark website for more details <a> https://www.clarku.edu</a>"
}
{
    "question": "does clark university offer stem opt for international studentes",
    "answer": "Yes, STEM OPT (Optional Practical Training) is available for international students."
}
{
    "question": "Hey",
    "answer": "Hello Clarkie, Feel free to ask me anything about Clark University."
}
{
    "question": "What is the tuition cost at clark university",
    "answer": "Tuition fees at Clark University can vary based on the program and student status. It's best to check their website for the most up-to-date information."
}
{
    "question": "tuition",
    "answer": "All applicants must complete the FAFSA (Free Application for Student Financial Aid) which can be completed https://studentaid.gov/h/apply-for-aid/. Please note that our Title IV code number is 002139. In addition to the FAFSA "
}
{
    "question": "cpt",
    "answer": "Students must complete two full-time semesters (does not include summer) in the United States before they qualify for CPT. Exceptions to the one academic year requirement are provided for students enrolled in graduate studies that require immediate participation in curricular practical training. "
}
{
    "question": "oncampus jobs",
    "answer": "All the on campus jobs are posted on Handshake. Please check the posted part time on campus jobs on Handshake. "
}
